[Music]
[Música]
Good evening family, good
muy buenas noches familia muy buenas
evening to everyone watching. It
noches a todos los que estáis viendo
turned out that
hecho subido a youtube resulta ser que
today it seems that
hoy parece que se ha filtrado
how much he earns has been leaked. And you're going to see. I'll also tell you
cuanto gana y vais a ver también os digo
one thing. I'll also tell you one thing.
una cosa también lo digo una cosa
This figure, this figure, no, it's not fixed, nor
esta cifra esta cifra no no es fija ni
is it the only thing that a person earns. Okay,
es lo único que gana una persona vale
this figure is from tweets. I don't know what
esta cifra es los de tuits no sé lo que
has been seen. Okay, but I imagine that
se habrá visto vale pero me imagino que
without meaning to, the screen has been seen
sin querer se la habrá visto la pantalla
and we'll
y
be seeing what he earns from tweets.
estaremos viendo lo que gana de tweets
But this would have to be added to his
pero esto habría que sumarle su canal de
YouTube channel, sponsorships, and so on. With
youtube patrocinios y demás yo con todo
all due respect to Ibai,
el respeto de todo el respeto a ibai
I hope you don't mind, but we're going to
espero que no le moleste pero vamos a
try to come up with a rough figure.
intentar hacer una cifra orientativa
Okay, let's see what has been
vale vamos a ver qué es lo que se ha
seen. And now I'll tell you,
visto y ahora os comento
with this, we're going to cut the total figure.
con esto vamos a recortar la cifra total
It's from SUVs. I'm going to x2 it, I'm
es de suvs voy a x 2
going to donate it and that will be the final figure.
lo voy a donar y va a ser la cifra final
And then we'll pass our people on to the Rubios.
y luego pasamos nuestra gente al rubios
Okay, this is what we're going to do.
vale esto lo que vamos a hacer
Currently, 22 thousand euros, 22, 20 ducklings,
actualmente 22 mil euros 22 20 patitos
which the web ducklings have finally
cual los patitos web al final han
raised by hand.  this is
recaudado a mano o sea esto es lo de
actually the thing about the fundraising for the
hecho lo de la recaudación para lo de la
palm tree as was being said before
palma que como se estaba diciendo antes
and I'm taking it if I had found out
y yo me llevo a si yo me llego a enterar
that I didn't know well for those who don't
que no me enteraba bueno para el que no
know why
lo sepa por qué
[Music]
[Música]
we're really sick these days something happened to me
estamos muy malitos estos días me pasó
kidney stones a lot
una cosita piedras en el riñón mucho
about how we're cursed these days
sobre lo que estamos malditos estos días
and I haven't found out about almost anything okay it's
y no me enterado de casi nada vale está
a little bit out of the way if I had
un poquito retirado si me hubiera
found out about this I would have asked them to
enterado de esto yo les hubiera pedido
participate and collaborate
participar y colaborar
with the few thousand that I could have
con los pocos mil de mente que yo
okay but my grain of
hubiera podido vale pero mi granito de
sand to put it
arena ponerlo
wat 22,000 euros 22,000 euros in the end I
wat 22.000 euros 22.000 euros al final
think I think that in the end for the palm tree
creo que creo que al final para la palma
almost 50 thousand almost 50,000
se ha recaudado casi 50 mil casi 50.000
but there's still the final burst
los pero queda la traca final
the final burst
la traca final
I don't know how many su we took hey the
yo no sé cuántas sus llevamos oye la
adoration that I'm going to put in here I'm going to put it in
adoración que voy a meter aquí voy a
through the exhaust pipe like the
meterla por el tubo de escape como el
macay tara I'm going to put it in your ass I'm
macay tara me lo voy a meter por el culo
going to put it in your ass bomb that they
se lo voy a meter por el culo bomba que
call it obviously through your ass we have the
lo llamen obviamente por el culo de vos
same  3000 psuv are welcome
igual tenemos 3000 psuv son bienvenidos
to all the people well so that I'm
a toda la gente bueno para que esté
watching this summarized on youtube
viendo esto resumido en youtube de
suddenly I just got a
repente me acabo de llevar una sorpresa
very pleasant surprise
muy grata
and juan guarnizo doesn't take out it's going to be a
y juan guarnizo no saca va a ser una
raid or a host I don't understand much the
raid o host yo que no entiendo mucho la
difference between raid kids I'm
diferencia entre raid hijos estoy
trying tweets I'm new to you and it's
probando tweets soy nuevo en tu y es
right now okay I come from youtube
ahora mismo vale yo vengo de youtube
[Music]
[Música]
and I don't really understand the difference
y no entiendo muy bien la diferencia
but suddenly it's blown up in fact
pero de repente se ha petado hecho de
suddenly 15,000 viewers have come here
repente han venido aquí 15.000
so from here one
espectadores así que desde aquí one
thank you very much now I'll put it to you on
muchísimas gracias ahora te lo pondré en
twitter also sending you a
twitter también te mando un abrazo
huge hug taking a interact soon
enorme tomando una relacionarme pronto
very soon be and around here we're going to have
muy prontito estar y por aquí que vamos
a little chat
a hacer una charlita
jabil beira host produces your channel on
jabil beira host produce tu canal en el
juan dry's channel send all the people to
canal de juan dry manda toda la gente a
your channel okay and what he's done almost or
tu canal vale y lo que ha hecho casi o
right I'm going to put an end to the result it comes to
right voy a poner fin al resultado viene
be more or less the same I'm not saying 2012
a ser más o menos lo mismo no digo 2012
van
van
boa calidade I'm out mateo you didn't
boa calidade estoy fuera mateo no me has
make me host it was done you did your best
hecho host se ha hecho ha hecho lo mejor
no
no
juan I owe you the kidney  juan i owe you a
juan te debo el riñón juan te debo un
kidney and i'm going to give you mine the one who
riñón y te voy a dar mi riñón el que
is sick the one who is screwing up my
está malo el que me estás jodiendo la
life with the stones
vida con las piedras
can look at the subsidies reason
puede mirar los subsidios motivo
welcome to all who live I by
bienvenidos a todos los que viven yo por
wang please follow me if you like
wang por favor seguirme si os gusta el
sanse and play here I had
sanse y toca aquí no perdía
absolutely nothing to lose no gossip about anything
absolutamente nada ningún chisme de nada
from the internet you will not regret it you
de internet no os arrepentiréis
will not regret it for
no os vais a arrepentir
a moment I was not talking to you through
un momento no me estaba hablando por
walsh and I do not want it I do not want it to be on
walsh y no quiero no quiero que será en
screen
pantalla
ah okay hayden with his miniature hayden
ah vale hayden con su miniatura hayden
with his miniatures okay
con sus miniaturas vale
very good idea very good idea what they
muy buena idea muy buena idea lo que me
are telling me of course guys come
están diciendo claro chavales que venir
by juán guarnizo those of you who come by juán
por juán guarnizo los que venís por juán
guarnizo I don't even know if they will
guarnizo no sé ni si seguirán aquí
still be here they still exist here in case
todavía se existen aquí todavía por si
you are interested
os interesa
since I am a fan of juana
ya que soy fan de de juana
I have on my secondary channel and on my
tengo en mi canal secundario y en mi
main channel
canal principal
an interview with juan
una entrevista juan
crema crema don't
crema
miss it okay you
crema no os lo podéis perder vale no os
can't miss it
lo podéis perder
well to keep it up I don't know how much he charges and we are not
bueno a mantener no sé cuánto cobra y no
going to stop the host issue
vamos a dejar ya el tema de host
is that I want to do it live people of
es que quiero hacerlo en directo gente
course I mean to have  the summary of the
claro o sea para tener el resumen de la
entire broadcast the summary of the broadcast
emisión entero el resumen de la emisión
as is roll one hundred percent everything has to be
tal cual rollo al cien por cien todo
cut and then come back I would have to
tiene que cortar y luego volver tendría
cut directly yeah but well it is
que cortar directo ajá pero bueno se
done you cut for
hace sea cortas
a second and besides the good thing about tweets
un segundo y aparte lo bueno de tweets
tweets has a very good thing that I
tweets tiene una cosa muy buena que me
like that youtube doesn't have youtube
gusta que no la tiene youtube youtube
when you cut a live stream
cuando tú cortas un directo
you have to start another one and it's another
tienes que empezar otro y es otro
live stream another link but what tweets has
directo otro link pero tweets lo que
is that when you port
tiene es que cuando portas
if you come back after 30 seconds it's as if
si vuelves a los 30 segundos es como si
nothing happened because people are
no hubiera pasado nada porque la gente
still there on the channel they understand me in the
sigue ahí en el canal me entiende en el
chat people continue if you don't move
chat sigue la gente si no te mueves no
nothing happens
pasa nada
in this interview juan ser take it out
en esta entrevista juan ser sácala
thanks flip out thank you very much
gracias flipa muchísimas gracias
you get analytics let's see
te salen analíticas a ver
and that where the [ __ ] is that how the [ __ ] do you
y eso donde pollas está eso como [__]
look at it to
se mira
see no it doesn't come out you have to cut to
a ver no no te sale tienes que cortar a
see there is
ver
a tab called
hay una pestaña que se llama sumario de
stream summary you have to cut
stream tienes que cortar
and select it's today's
y selecciona es el de hoy
channel analysis
análisis del canal
[Laughter]
[Risas]
but I was going there
pero yo iba ahí
but I was there
pero iba ahí
like the [ __ ] how the [ __ ] I was going
como [__]
there I was
como [__] iba ahí
can buy my house
ibai puede comprar mi casa
[Music]
[Música]
rival takes it there he can buy my house
rival lo lleva ahí puede comprar mi casa
today only with what the  witch
hoy únicamente con lo que gana the witch
flower and the other day let's see many times I
flor y el otro día a ver muchas veces lo
explained it, I mean, these people are titans
explicaba o sea esta gente son titanes
titans
titanes
the salaries of these people don't make
los sueldos de esta gente no tiene
sense they talk to each other
sentido se hablan
this is tweets
esto es tweets
this is tweet
esto es tweet
for tweets then they have YouTube their
para tweets luego tiene youtube su canal
YouTube channel which is good I hope you don't
de youtube que bueno espero que no le
mind but let's see let's do
moleste pero vamos a ver vamos a hacer
a calculation of what it could be okay
un cálculo de lo que podría ser vale
let's do a calculation of what it
vamos a hacer un cálculo de lo que
could be and vice and vice if I'm not
podría ser y vice y vice si no me
mistaken has the main by channel
equivoco tiene el canal de by principal
okay we're talking about 86
vale que estamos hablando de 86
almost 87 million visits this is
casi 87 millones de visitas estos son
between 70 and 90 thousand euros
entre 70 y 90 mil euros
worth between 70 and 90 thousand euros and it's not
vale entre 70 y 90 mil euros y es que no
sustainable also the channel
se sostiene también el canal de
chatting chatting quietly
charlando charlando tranquilamente
from those 6 million
desde esos 6 millones
five thousand euros seven thousand euros around
cinco mil euros siete mil euritos por
there
ahí
okay then
vale entonces
you know what we're missing we're missing the
sabéis que nos falta nos faltan los
sponsorships we're missing the sponsorships
patrocinios nos faltan los patrocinios
which are the sponsorships the brands
que son los patrocinios las marcas
when he was going to collaborate with cola cao and they don't
cuando iba a colaborar con cola cao y no
open the package the bastard when he was going to
abren el paquete el cabrón cuando iba a
collaborate
colaborar
with netflix what he did those are already
con netflix lo que hizo esos son ya
impressive amounts too okay and
cantidades impresionantes también vale y
vice can buy an island
vice puede comprarse una isla
surely imagine  aurum play dude
seguramente imaginaros aurum play tío
but I was there how the [ __ ] have you gone
pero iba ahí como [__] se te ha ido
already opened that
ya ha abierto eso
leon already thank you very much
leon ya muchísimas gracias
and to think that amount they take away almost
y pensar que esa cantidad le quitan casi
half of taxes in Spain almost
la mitad de impuestos en españa casi la
half no karime half
mitad no karime la mitad
look at you what a pain to get
fíjate tú qué putada
because this has arrived he and his
llegar porque esto ha llegado él y sus
balls has managed to buy has
[__] ha conseguido comprar ha
managed to get to this and lana in fact
conseguido llegar a esto y lana de hecho
puts his balls okay but look at you what a
pone sus [__] vale pero fíjate tú qué
pain that you get to collect this
putada que llegues a cobrar esto
and Spain comes and tells you tomás for
y venga españa y te diga tomás por la
half
mitad
the p s 5 well I wouldn't know how much they
la p s 5 pues yo no sabría cuánto le
pay these people acne for the promo
pagan a esta gente al acné por la promo
I'm honest for a promo they
yo soy sincero a mi por una promo
normally pay me 500 euros thousand euros
normalmente me pagan 500 euros mil euros
and maybe a good company
y acaso una empresa buena
three hundred euros
trescientos euros
700 you know things like that but these people these
700 sabes cosas así pero esta gente esta
people I think they pay them like 20 30
gente yo creo que le pagan como 20 30
thousand it
mil
depends but how the hell did you fall and vice
depende pero cómo [__] has caído y vice
get into getting into this page and in
meterte con meterte en esta página y en
the middle of live churra and selections in
pleno directo churra y selecciones en de
today's
hoy
analysis of the channel that web that a ball
análisis del canal que web que un huevo
man
tío
you have balls
tienes huevos
43 increases the realize not a
43 aumenta los daros cuenta tampoco una
big surprise either  I tell you, it's
gran sorpresa también os digo
not a surprise to
o sea tampoco una sorpresa
realize that he has 443,500
daros cuenta que él tiene 443 mil 500
subscribers,
suscriptores
for every 40, for each subscriber more or
por cada 40 por cada suscriptor más o
less it's three euros, not
menos son tres euros no
three euros, we couldn't say
tres euros no podríamos decir
for each subscriber it's three euros, well you
por cada suscriptor son tres euros pues
can do the math, Lamac in
puedes hacer la cuenta lamac en
subscribers, because he already has
suscriptores pues ya lleva
[Music]
[Música]
well he doesn't charge much for ads, Ibagué
pues no cobra mucho por anuncios ibagué
and he's going to go for ads, he won't put in
y va a ir por anuncios no le meterá
many ads
muchos anuncios
because we're talking about what
porque estamos hablando de qué
I think is more, I think it's more, I'm
yo creo que es más yo creo que es más os
going to explain why because these will
voy a explicar por qué porque éstos
surely be 28 days,
seguramente sean 28 días
not 30 days, the last 30 days,
no 30 días los últimos 30 días
but let's
pero vamos
put it that for subscriptions he charges
ponerlo que por suscripciones cobra
80,000 or 90 thousand euros and the rest up to
80.000 ó 90 mil euros y el resto hasta
this, well, are the ads and the beats
esto pues son los anuncios y los beats
and so on, a weak month,
y así un mes flojo
so a weak month, a
así un mes flojo
summary of the stream
sumario de stream
and this is what is generated for the entire month, the
y esto es lo que generado de todo el mes
entire month, I have to give this,
de todo el mes tengo que dar esto
just like it is in this person, the
al igual que es en esto persona los
balls,
[__]
then having day,
luego haber día
week,
semana
export data,
exportar datos
seven hours of live, guys, seven
siete horas de directo chicos siete
hours of live
horas de directo
that I haven't done, you feel faith,
que no llevo sientes faith
but since he doesn't know, and he's going to  go
pero como no sabe y va a ir
but since he doesn't know and goes there
pero como no sabe y va ahí
if you get in there it comes out if even I've been
si te metes ahí te sale si los hasta yo
trying twitch for two days
que llevo dos días probando twitch
how long have I been
cuánto tiempo llevo
and subscriptions
y suscripciones
ok propose it
vale lo propongas
again I put it here
de nuevo yo lo pongo aquí
to see nothing happens either
a ver no pasa nada tampoco
neither let's see nothing happens it is done it is
tampoco a ver no pasa nada se hace
understood that that money is earned no
se entiende que se gana ese dinero no
good
bueno
44 thousand subscriptions worth
44 mil suscripciones vale
4 thousand subscriptions 4 thousand 56
4 mil suscripciones 4 mil 56
2700 prime
2700 prime
455 in total let's add up that there are missing
455 en total vamos a sumar que faltan
subs okay let's add up that let's add up that there are
subs vale vamos a sumar que vamos a
missing subs I
sumar que faltan subs
don't know how it is in Spanish you Javier to a
no sé cómo es en español tú javier a un
parallel he already knows the accounting action xd
paralela ya él se la acción contable xd
not the parquet the erectus and you think
no el parqué la erectus y tú te crees
that someone makes the
que alguien se hace la declaración de la
income tax return alone of course
renta el solo
an accountant does it for me everything is
claro que me lo hace un contable a todo
done by an accountant even the most to
se le hace un contable hasta el mas
provide them by an accountant even if they earn a
brindárselas un contable aunque ganen
thousand euros a month an accountant does it what the
mil euros al mes se lo hace un contable
hell am I going to be the
que [__] voy a ser yo la declaración de
income tax return
la renta
I don't have it the store managers are paid
yo no tengo se le paga a los gestores
that  does for that has studied
stores que lo hace para eso ha estudiado
like what he does I don't know what to
como lo que hace yo no sé lo que hay que
do I tell the fact all the
hacer yo le digo al hecho todas las
bills that I have collected I send it to him all
facturas que he cobrado se lo mando todo
this is what I have collected and this one
esto es lo que he cobrado y éste me
buys me a microphone and I have bought a
compra un micro y me he comprado un
laptop
portátil
many times apart no longer that you don't know it
muchas veces aparte ya no que no sepáis
's normal that you don't know and that you speak
es normal que no sepáis y que habléis
without knowing but why do you speak because he
sin saber pero por qué habláis porque
speaks and in that way man why do you have to
habla y de esa forma tío porque tenéis
lack respect
que falta el respeto
why do you speak insulting on top of that
por qué habláis insultando encima
I respect
yo respeto
respect we would always
respeto siempre
be talking about approximately
estaríamos hablando de aproximadamente
how much we could be talking about clear
cuánto podríamos estar hablando claro
this I don't know if you can see everything
esto no sé si se puede ver todo lo que
generated outside of the SUVs which is the
generado fuera de las suvs que es la
vast majority but let's do a
gran mayoría pero vamos a hacer un
rounding up okay
redondeo por arriba vale
let's be clear now the SUVs are worth
vamos a poner claro ahora las suvs valen
less but how much can this be this is
menos pero cuánto puede ser esto es de
100 thousand and
100 mil y
4 thousand 56
4 mil 56
five thousand euros no now the sub are worth
cinco mil euros no ahora las sub valen
less five thousand let's see which one of course
menos cinco mil vamos a ver cuál claro
now the sub are worth less that's why
ahora la sub valen menos por eso la
also the forty something thousand his
también los cuarenta y tantos mil sus
that he has
que tiene
no I'm not liquid don't worry don't
no no estoy líquido no te preocupes no
worry mateo diego the knicks
te preocupes mateo diego los knicks no
nothing has come out man
ha salido nada tío
but change  the word of the draw I'll be back
pero cambia la palabra del sorteo vuelvo
later no longer today
ya luego ya no hoy
they know that the duty to share this don't
saben que el deber de compartir esto no
[ __ ] with me you can't
me jodas
share it you can't not
no se puede compartir no se puede
even let you tweets in those
ni siquiera te deja tweets en esos
terms and conditions it doesn't let you what an
términos y condiciones no te deja
ally she has today the ivai they are going
vaya aliada que lleva hoy el ivai lo van
to handle it gave tomorrow it has passed and it goes and they are going
a manejar dio mañana ha pasado y va y lo
to handle it because you can't
van a manejar porque no se puede mostrar
even show how much you earn it's true you can't you can't
ni cuánto ganas es verdad no se puede
show how much you earn but
no se puede mostrar cuánto gana pero
escape today he ate a [ __ ] but
escaparte hoy se comió una [__] pero
literally got well support us I can
literal sacó bien apóyanos lo puedo
show it on my twitter you can see the clip
mostrar en mi twitter podéis ver el clip
on my twitter for those who don't know it is
en mi twitter para quien no sepa tiene
on my twitter because there are a lot of
en mi twitter porque hay aquí mucha
new people here now at javier oliveira
gente nueva ahora arroba javier oliveira
couple vi oliveira on my twitter what was
pareja vi oliveira en mi twitter lo
shared I took out I took out an ep guy
compartido saco saco me un ep tío ha
opened twitter and one supports him that
abierto twitter y una apoya así de
big guy
grande tío
a [ __ ] that big he will be tired and
una [__] así de grande estará cansado y
now it will be time exhausted with all the hours that he
ahora tocará agotado con todas las horas
has stuck and live damn he will
que se ha pegado y en directo
take you out or tea
[__] te sacará o té
said damn you
dicha [__] te
salty he ran and read
sala corrió y lea
and took
y le
out a [ __ ] this does not support
sacó de una [__] esto no apoya
literally and he read it
literalmente y le lea
and that cannot be taught to see I do
y eso no se puede enseñar a ver yo
not think they are worth it either because  teach that is that
tampoco creo que te valen porque enseñe
you come very strict with the
es que tú vienes muy estricto con las
rules
normas
this is what I was going to say now
esto es iba a decir yo ahora os enseño
I will also show you what I earn come on it goes
yo también lo que yo gano venga va
to tweets I will show you what I earn in
en tweets os enseño lo que yo gano en
tweets
tweets
I get wet
me mojo
for boxes encourage yourself and do oops
para casillas animéis y os hagáis oops
on Javi's twitter it appears
en el twitter de javi me aparece
suspended it's me not Javier Oliveira
suspendido soy yo no javier oliveira
Sebas Javier Oliveira Javi Oliveira is
sebas javier oliveira javi oliveira está
suspended he earns 300 euros well yes around
suspendido gana 300 euros pues si por
there he earned in tweets yes yes let's see I
ahí ganó en tweets sí sí a ver yo lo
show ours but it's not
muestro los nuestros pero que no se
possible but come on I say it in tweets what he
puede pero vamos lo digo yo en tweets lo
got me is 300 euros things like that
que me sacó son 300 euros cosas así
habit they suspended the twitter account
hábito suspendieron la cuenta de twitter
don't [ __ ] with me I haven't
no me jodas
done anything support it's not here it's
no he hecho nada apoyo no está aquí está
here this is my twitter account
aquí esta es mi cuenta de twitter
nothing has been done guys it's in my
se han hecho nada chavales está en mi
twitter account I'm
cuenta de twitter
not going to show you any more down
no os voy a mostrar más para abajo
because let's see if I'm going to eat my ass
porque a ver si me voy a comer el nepe
okay
yo vale
now let's see now better what Ricky
ahora vemos ahora mejor lo de ricky
edited on youtube it's legal but not on
edite en youtube es legal pero no en
youtube yes a lot of encouragement from Andalusia and
youtube si mucho animo desde andalucía y
great initiative  and the rest of stream
gran iniciativa y el resto de stream
and vice
y vice
and go and he doesn't study churra
y vaya y no estudia churra
the boat the nickname has to be changed Iván
el bote el nick hay que cambiarlo iván
Iván fix it
iván arreglarlo
yes
sí
Javier Oliveira Javier Oliveira change
javier oliveira javier oliveira cambiar
the moderators there you can see the piece
los moderadores ahí podéis ver la pedazo
of dick that is something alive and dance but
de [__] que es algo vivo y baile pero
a chicken like that is an almost victimizing chicken like that
un pollo así es un pollo casi victimario
and a chicken like that
así y un pollo así
and go don't talk to me as a joke or whoever
y vas no me hables por guasa o quien
is talking on WhatsApp because I have it
esté hablando por whatsapp porque lo
here loading now I take it
tengo aquí cargando ahora lo cojo
last night 400 beware and today 4,000 well nothing
anoche 400 beware y hoy 4.000 pues nada
Pablo what happens to me a lot
pablo que me le ocurra mucho
that I have made some really good content and
que he hecho un contenido buenísimo y la
people are appreciating it
gente lo está agradeciendo
is that to me guys, I mean, liquidate it,
es que a mí chicos es decir liquidarlo
what do you win when it is already known is that I
qué ganas cuando ya se sabe es que lo
said it in saves for example if you
dije en salvados por ejemplo si tú
have 30 thousand or 40 thousand subs although now they are
tienes 30 mil o 40 mil subs aunque ahora
worth less, it is that people can make
valgan menos es que la gente puede hacer
an calculation of what it is really expensive
un cálculo de lo que es realmente caro
more or less it is known, that is why what I am
más o menos se sabe por eso lo que estoy
saying is not that it is a
diciendo yo que tampoco es que sea la
big
gran
thing to know it
cosa saberlo
Javi do you think it goes more for the issue
javi tú crees que vaya más por el tema
of confidentiality I do not understand what it
de la confidencialidad no entiendo qué
matters to you tweets that each one
le importa tweets que cada uno diga lo
say what you earn I don't understand what it matters to you twist that each one says what they earn what it matters because it breaks the rule there could be now much less now in fact this month it comes to me 106 thousand dollars and the previous one it was 140 thousand but I said it in saves of course more or less it
yo lo dije en salvados claro más o menos
is what you can earn no people can
es lo que puedes ganar no la gente puede
calculate I did not think it was that illegal
calcular no pensaba que era tan ilegal
I am going banned from I am going
me voy baneado de
banned no I do not think that is the
me voy baneado no no creo que eso sea
way
manera
well to believe no I do not think this is okay
bueno creer no no creo que esto sea vale
or not there are already
o no
people who were liquidated in the
ya hay gente que la liquidada en la
last one walk already the other way around
pasada andar ya al revés
the last one already revealed that
la pasada ya reveló que aparece
Valentino improvements appear well the thing is that people
valentino mejoras pues es que la gente
literally know what an SUV costs
literalmente sabe lo que cuesta una suv
and the SUVs are you can already see them UBs that I have that has
y las suvs son ya puedes verlas ubs que
one that has such you
tengo yo que tiene a uno que tiene tal
know the tweet stranger
sabes el tuit stranger
what I do not understand is
lo que yo no entiendo es
how tweets tracker knows the SUVs that they have that
como tweets tracker sabe las suvs que
people have
que tiene la gente
like tweets tracker knows the apps that
como tweets tracker sabe las apps que
others have
tienen los demás
if the tweet tracker is not
si el tuit tracker no es
[Music] it
[Música]
is not official it could be because of the
no es oficial puede ser por los
advertisers because of the approximate
anunciantes por el aproximado
but it is not exact either exact no  you
pero tampoco es exacto exacto no lo
can calculate it never worth it because you
puedes calcular nunca vale porque tú
know the SUV that has is worth 45,000 subs
sabes la suv que tiene vale 45.000 subs
okay so let's say that from there you get it let's
vale pues digamos que de ahí saca
see now they are worth less of course sixty
a ver ahora valen menos claro sesenta
thousand euros 60,000 70,000 80,000 okay but
mil euros 60.000 70.000 80.000 vale pero
you can't calculate
tú no puedes calcular
how many dancing
cuántos bailando
and you can't calculate the ads you
y lo de los anuncios no lo puedes
understand let's see more or less yes
me entiende a ver más o menos sí
but in this way I also don't understand
pero de esta manera tampoco entiendo por
why that is illegal or what happens what happens I
qué eso es ilegal o sea qué pasa
put whatever I want
qué pasa yo pongo lo que me dé la gana
no if I want to say how much I earn because I ca
no si yo quiero decir cuánto gano porque
n't say if I want to do for
no lo puedo decir si yo quiero hacer por
example how and vice versa that this is a
ejemplo cómo y vice que esto es un acto
charity event and suddenly I want to say hey
benéfico y de repente quiero decir oye
for everything we earn today it goes to the
por todo lo que ganemos hoy va para la
palm
palma
because I can't
porque no puedo
what nonsense what nonsense
qué tontería qué tontería
well let's see what you
bueno vamos a ver qué es lo que me
're telling me karime to you know what you
estáis diciendo karime a tú sabes qué es
're telling me about ricky that we
lo que me están diciendo de ricky de que
watch a video let's go to the next
veamos un vídeo vamos al siguiente
extract family don't go
extracto familia no os vayáis
[Music]
[Música]